<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Praktikum App F1</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_race">Race</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="more_info_btn">Check it out!</string>

    <string name="creator_name">Ibrahim Nur Huda</string>
    <string name="creator_NIM">L0122076</string>
    <string name="creator_prodi">Informatika, 22</string>
    <string name="creator_fakultas">Fakultas Teknologi Informasi dan Sains Data</string>
    <string name="creator_univ">Universitas Sebelas Maret</string>
    <string name="creator_email">ibrahimnrhd@student.uns.ac.id</string>

    <string name="home_event_title">Home</string>
    <string name="home_event_desc">
        A one stop schedule app to track all the Formula 1 events of the year for the year of 2024. This app includes
        info for all 24 races from the rounds, name, date, image of the track, brief description, and a button
        that links to the Formula 1 website for even more details about the Grand Prix history, statistics,
        former winner, former pole positions, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="home_event_app_title">F1 Schedule 2024 Season App</string>
    <string name="home_event_briefDesc">More info about Formula 1 2024 Season!</string>

    <string name="fav_circuit_title"><b>My Favorite Circuit</b></string>
    <string name="fav_circuit_name">Spa-Francorchamps</string>
    <string name="fav_circuit_desc"><b>Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps</b>\n
        (French pronunciation: [siʁkɥi də spa fʁɑ̃kɔʁʃɑ̃]), informally referred to as Spa,[1][2] is a 7.004 km (4.352 mi)
        motor-racing circuit located in Francorchamps, Stavelot, Wallonia, Belgium, about 8 km (5.0 mi) southeast of Spa.
        It is the current venue of the Formula One Belgian Grand Prix, hosting its first Grand Prix in 1925, and has held
        a Grand Prix every year since 1985 except 2003 and 2006.
    </string>
    <string name="btnToGithub">My Github!</string>
    <string name="btnToInstagram">My Instagram!</string>
    <string name="btnToShare">Share My Profile!</string>

    <string name="briefDesc">Check out my LinkTree!</string>

    <string name="tv_circuit_name">This is Circuit Name</string>

    <string name="tab_text_1">Calendar</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Driver</string>


    <string name="race_name">Nama Balapan</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="btnToF1">Check out on formula1.com</string>
    <string name="detailedDescText">
        Using the button below you can find the full weekend schedule, including details of practice and qualifying sessions, support races,
        press conferences and special events, plus the latest news headlines, circuit information and F1 race results.\n\nYou can also find
        broadcast information, with details of how and where you can watch the race on TV by clicking on the button below!
    </string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Round 1 - Bahrain Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 2 - Saudi Arabian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 3 - Australian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 4 - Japanese Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 5 - Chinese Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 6 - Miami Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 7 - Emilia-Romagna Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 8 - Grand Prix De Monaco</item>
        <item>Round 9 - Canadian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 10 - Spanish Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 11 - Austrian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 12 - British Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 13 - Hungarian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 14 - Belgian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 15 - Dutch Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 16 - Italian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 17 - Azerbaijan Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 18 - Singapore Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 19 - US Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 20 - Mexican Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 21 - Brazilian Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 22 - Las Vegas Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 23 - Qatar Grand Prix</item>
        <item>Round 24 - Abu Dhabi Grand Prix</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_full_name">
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Gulf Air Bahrain Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 STC Saudi Arabian Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Rolex Australian Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 MSC Cruises Japanese Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Lenovo Chinese Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 CRYPTO.COM Miami Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 MSC Cruises Gran Premio Del Made in Italy E Dell\'Emilia-Romagna Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Grand Prix De Monaco 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 AWS Grand Prix Du Canada 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Aramco Gran Premio De Espana 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Qatar Airways Austrian Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Qatar Airways British Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Hungarian Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Rolex Belgian Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Heineken Dutch Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Pirelli Gran Premio D\'Italia 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Qatar Airways Azerbaijan Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Singapore Airlines Singapore Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Pirelli United States Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Gran Premio De La Ciudad De Mexico 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Lenovo Grande Premio De Sao Paulo 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Heineken Silver Las Vegas Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula Qatar Airways Qatar Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Formula 1 Etihad Airways Abu Dhabi Grand Prix 2024]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_date">
        <item>29 Feb - 02 Mar</item>
        <item>07 Mar - 09 Mar</item>
        <item>22 Mar - 24 Mar</item>
        <item>05 Apr - 07 Apr</item>
        <item>19 Apr - 21 Apr</item>
        <item>03 May - 05 May</item>
        <item>17 May - 19 May</item>
        <item>24 May - 26 May</item>
        <item>07 Jun - 09 Jun</item>
        <item>21 Jun - 23 Jun</item>
        <item>28 Jun - 30 Jun</item>
        <item>05 Jul - 07 Jul</item>
        <item>19 Jul - 21 Jul</item>
        <item>26 Jul - 28 Jul</item>
        <item>23 Aug - 25 Aug</item>
        <item>30 Aug - 01 Sep</item>
        <item>13 Sep - 15 Sep</item>
        <item>20 Sep - 22 Sep</item>
        <item>18 Oct - 20 Oct</item>
        <item>24 Oct - 27 Oct</item>
        <item>01 Nov - 03 Nov</item>
        <item>21 Nov - 23 Nov</item>
        <item>29 Nov - 01 Dec</item>
        <item>06 Dec - 08 Dec</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_img">
        <item>@drawable/bahraingp</item>
        <item>@drawable/saudiarabiangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/australiangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/japanesegp</item>
        <item>@drawable/chinagp</item>
        <item>@drawable/miamigp</item>
        <item>@drawable/emiliaromagnagp</item>
        <item>@drawable/monacogp</item>
        <item>@drawable/canadagp</item>
        <item>@drawable/spaingp</item>
        <item>@drawable/austriangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/britishgp</item>
        <item>@drawable/hungariangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/belgiangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/dutchgp</item>
        <item>@drawable/italiangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/azerbaijangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/singaporegp</item>
        <item>@drawable/usgp</item>
        <item>@drawable/mexicangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/braziliangp</item>
        <item>@drawable/lasvegasgp</item>
        <item>@drawable/qatargp</item>
        <item>@drawable/abudhabigp</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="data_web">
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Bahrain.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Saudi_Arabia.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Australia.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Japan.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/China.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Miami.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/EmiliaRomagna.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Monaco.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Canada.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Spain.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Austria.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Great_Britain.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Hungary.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Belgium.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Netherlands.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Italy.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Azerbaijan.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Singapore.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/United_States.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Mexico.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Brazil.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Las_Vegas.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/Qatar.html</item>
        <item>https://www.formula1.com/en/racing/2024/United_Arab_Emirates.html</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_desc">
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Bahrain International Circuit\nThe Bahrain Grand Prix, officially known as the Gulf Air
        Bahrain Grand Prix for sponsorship reasons, is a Formula One motor racing event in Bahrain. The first race took
        place at the Bahrain International Circuit on 4 April 2004. It made history as the first Formula One Grand Prix
        to be held in the Middle East, and was given the award for the "Best Organised Grand Prix" by the FIA.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Jeddah Corniche Circuit\nThe Saudi Arabian Grand Prix (Arabic: جائزة السعودية الكبرى)
        is a Formula One motor racing event which took place for the first time in 2021.
        The inaugural edition of the race was held in Jeddah, in Saudi Arabia.
        It was the fifth full-night race title on the Formula One calendar, following the Singapore,
        Bahrain, Sakhir and Qatar Grands Prix.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Albert Partk Circuit\nThe Australian Grand Prix is an annual motor racing event
        which is under contract to host Formula One until 2035. One of the oldest surviving motorsport competitions
        held in Australia, the Grand Prix has moved frequently with 23 different venues having been used since it
        was first run at Phillip Island in 1928. The race became part of the Formula One World Championship in 1985.
        Since 1996, it has been held at the Albert Park Circuit in Melbourne, with the exceptions of 2020 and 2021,
        when the races were cancelled due to the COVID-19 pandemic. Before that, it was held in Adelaide.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Suzuka Circuit\nThe Japanese Grand Prix is a motor racing event in the calendar of
        the Formula One World Championship. Historically, Japan has been one of the last races of the season, and
        as such the Japanese Grand Prix has been the venue for many title-deciding races, with 13 World Drivers\'
        Champions being crowned over the 36 World Championship Japanese Grands Prix that have been hosted. Japan
        was the only Asian nation to host a Formula One race (including the Pacific Grand Prix) until Malaysia
        joined the calendar in 1999.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Shanghai International Circuit\nThe Chinese Grand Prix (Chinese: 中国大奖赛; pinyin:
        Zhōngguó Dàjiǎngsài) is a round of the Formula One World Championship. The event was held every year from 2004
        until 2019 and is contracted to be held until 2025. The event was suspended from 2020 to 2023 due to the COVID-19
        pandemic in China.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Miami International Autodrome\n
        The Miami Grand Prix is a Formula One Grand Prix which was held for the first time during the 2022 season,
        with the event taking place at the Miami International Autodrome on a ten-year contract.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Autodromo Intenazionale Enzo e Dino Ferrari\n
        The Emilia Romagna Grand Prix is a Formula One motor racing event held at the Autodromo Internazionale Enzo e
        Dino Ferrari, often referred to as "Imola" after the town where it is located.The event takes the name
        "Emilia-Romagna" from the Italian region where the circuit is located. The venue has previously hosted the
        Italian Grand Prix in 1980, and the San Marino Grand Prix from 1981 to 2006.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit de Monaco\n
        The Monaco Grand Prix is a Formula One motor racing event held annually on the Circuit de Monaco, in late May
        or early June. Run since 1929, it is widely considered to be one of the most important and prestigious
        automobile races in the world, and is one of the races—along with the Indianapolis 500 and the 24 Hours of
        Le Mans—that form the Triple Crown of Motorsport. It is the only Grand Prix that does not adhere to the FIA\'s
        mandated 305-kilometre (190-mile) minimum race distance for F1 races.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit Gilles Villeneuve\n
        The Canadian Grand Prix is an annual motor racing event held since 1961. It has been part of the Formula One
        World Championship since 1967. It was first staged at Mosport Park in Bowmanville, Ontario, as a sports car
        event, before alternating between Mosport and Circuit Mont-Tremblant, Quebec, after Formula One took over the
        event. After 1971, safety concerns led to the Grand Prix moving permanently to Mosport. In 1978, after similar
        safety concerns with Mosport, the Canadian Grand Prix moved to its current home at Circuit Gilles Villeneuve
        on Notre Dame Island in Montreal, Quebec.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya\n
        The Spanish Grand Prix is a Formula One motor racing event currently held at the Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya.
        The race is one of the oldest in the world still contested, celebrating its centenary in 2013. The race had
        modest beginnings as a production car race. Interrupted by the First World War, the race waited a decade for
        its second running before becoming a staple of the European calendar. In 1927 it was part of the World
        Manufacturers\' Championship; it was promoted to the European Championship in 1935 before the Spanish Civil War
        brought an end to racing. The race was successfully revived in 1967 and has been a regular part of the
        Formula One World Championship since 1968 (except 1982–1985) at a variety of venues.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Red Bull Ring\n
        The Austrian Grand Prix is a Fédération Internationale de l\'Automobile sanctioned motor racing event that
        was held in 1964, 1970–1987, 1997–2003, and then returned to the Formula One calendar in 2014.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Silverstone Circuit\n
        The British Grand Prix is a Grand Prix motor racing event organised in the United Kingdom by Motorsport UK.
        First held by the Royal Automobile Club (RAC) in 1926, the British Grand Prix has been held annually since
        1948 and has been a round of the FIA Formula One World Championship every year since 1950. In 1952, following
        the transfer of the lease of the Silverstone Circuit to the British Racing Drivers\' Club,[1] the RAC
        delegated the organisation of races held at Silverstone to the BRDC,[2] and those held at Aintree to the
        British Automobile Racing Club.[3] This arrangement lasted until the RAC created the Motor Sports Association
        in the late 1970s and it reclaimed organising control of the event. The RAC MSA was renamed Motorsport UK in
        2019 when it formally split from the RAC.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Hungaroring\n
        The Hungarian Grand Prix (Hungarian: Magyar Nagydíj) is a motor racing event held annually in Mogyoród at
        the Hungaroring. Since 1986, the race has been a round of the FIA Formula One World Championship. The first
        Hungarian Grand Prix was held on 21 June 1936 over a 5-kilometre (3.1-mile) track laid out in Népliget, a
        park in Budapest. The Mercedes-Benz, Auto Union, and the Alfa Romeo-equipped Ferrari teams all sent three
        cars and the event drew a very large crowd. However, politics and the ensuing war meant the end of Grand Prix
        motor racing in the country for fifty years.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps\n
        The Belgian Grand Prix (French: Grand Prix de Belgique; Dutch: Grote Prijs van België; German: Großer Preis
        von Belgien) is a motor racing event which forms part of the Formula One World Championship. The first national
        race of Belgium was held in 1925 at the Spa region\'s race course, an area of the country that had been
        associated with motor sport since the very early years of racing. To accommodate Grand Prix motor racing,
        the Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps race course was built in 1921 but until 1924 it was used only for motorcycle
        racing. After the 1923 success of the new 24 hours of Le Mans in France, the Spa 24 Hours, a similar 24-hour
        endurance race, was run at the Spa track.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit Zandvoort\n
        The Dutch Grand Prix (Dutch: Grote Prijs van Nederland) is an annual Formula One World Championship auto
        racing event, held at Circuit Zandvoort, North Holland, the Netherlands, from 1950 through 1985, and after a
        35 year hiatus, from 2021 onwards. It has been a part of the Formula One World Championship since 1952, and
        was designated the European Grand Prix twice, in 1962 and 1976, when this title was an honorary designation
        given each year to one Grand Prix race in Europe.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Autodromo Nazionale di Monza\n
        The Italian Grand Prix (Italian: Gran Premio d\'Italia) is the fifth oldest national motor racing Grand Prix
        (after the French Grand Prix, the United States Grand Prix, the Spanish Grand Prix and the Russian Grand Prix),
        having been held since 1921. Since 2013, it has been the Grand Prix held the most times, with 93 editions as of
        2023. It is one of the two Grands Prix (along with the British) which has run as an event of the Formula One
        World Championship Grands Prix every season, continuously since the championship was introduced in 1950. Every
        Formula One Italian Grand Prix in the World Championship era has been held at Monza except in 1980, when it was
        held at Imola.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Baku City Circuit\n
        The Azerbaijan Grand Prix (Azerbaijani: Azərbaycan Qran Prisi) is a Formula One motor racing event that was
        held for the first time in 2017. It is held on the Baku City Circuit, a street circuit in Baku, the capital
        of Azerbaijan. The first Formula One Grand Prix to be held in Azerbaijan was the 2016 European Grand Prix,
        which took place at the Baku City Circuit. A year later, in 2017, the same venue hosted the first Azerbaijan
        Grand Prix. The race was held on 25 June and was one of five races to be held on a street circuit during the
        2017 Formula One season, along with the Singapore, Monaco, Australian and Canadian Grands Prix. The first
        Azerbaijan Grand Prix winner was Daniel Ricciardo of Red Bull, grabbing his first win of the 2017 campaign
        during Sunday\'s Azerbaijan Grand Prix.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Marina Bay Street Circuit\n
        The Singapore Grand Prix is a motor racing event which forms part of the Formula One World Championship.
        The event takes place on the Marina Bay Street Circuit and was the inaugural night race and first street
        circuit in Asia designed for Formula One races.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Circuit of the Americas\n
        The United States Grand Prix is a motor racing event that has been held on and off since 1908, when it was
        known as the American Grand Prize. The Grand Prix later became part of the Formula One World Championship.
        As of 2023, the Grand Prix has been held 52 times at ten different locations. Since 2012, it has been held
        every year at the Circuit of the Americas in Austin, Texas, except in 2020 when it was cancelled due to the
        COVID-19 pandemic.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Autódromo Hermanos Rodríguez\n
        The Mexican Grand Prix (Spanish: Gran Premio de México), currently held under the name Mexico City Grand Prix
        (Spanish: Gran Premio de la Ciudad de México), is a motor racing event held at the Autódromo Hermanos Rodríguez
        in Mexico City. It first appeared as a non-championship event in 1962 before being held as a championship event
        in 1963–1970 and 1986–1992. The Grand Prix returned in 2015 at the Mexico City circuit.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Autódromo José Carlos Pace\n
        The Brazilian Grand Prix (Portuguese: Grande Prêmio do Brasil), currently held under the name São Paulo Grand
        Prix (Portuguese: Grande Prêmio de São Paulo), is a Formula One championship race which is currently held at
        the Autódromo José Carlos Pace in Interlagos neighborhood, Cidade Dutra, São Paulo.Formula 1 Lenovo Grande
        Premio De Sao Paulo 2024]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Las Vegas Strip Circuit\n
        The Las Vegas Grand Prix is a motor racing event that forms part of the Formula One World Championship, taking
        place in Paradise, Nevada, in the United States. It is conducted as a night race on a temporary street circuit
        that includes parts of the Las Vegas Strip. The first race was held on November 18, 2023. Formula One and Las
        Vegas have signed a ten-year agreement for the race.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Losail International Circuit\n
        The Qatar Grand Prix is a Formula One motor racing event which is held in Qatar. It was held for the first time
        on 21 November as part of the 2021 championship at the Lusail International Circuit, and after not taking place
        during the 2022 season due to the 2022 FIFA World Cup taking place in Qatar, it rejoined the calendar in 2023
        under a 10-year contract. The race was established as the fourth full-night race (as opposed to day or
        day-to-night races) on the Formula One calendar, following the Singapore, Bahrain and Sakhir Grands Prix.]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[Location: Yas Marina Circuit\n
        The Abu Dhabi Grand Prix (Arabic: سباق جائزة أبوظبي الكبرى) is a Formula One motor racing event. The first race
        took place on 1 November 2009, held at the Hermann Tilke-designed Yas Marina Circuit on Yas Island, near Abu
        Dhabi, the capital of the United Arab Emirates.]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>